Charles Darwin once said “A man who dares to waste one hour of time has not discovered the value of life”.
查尔斯·达尔文曾说过：“敢于浪费一小时时间的人，还没有发现生命的价值。”
If you live one hundred years, that only equates to twelve-hundred months – and when you break it down even further into days, hours and minutes, it gets more frightening.
如果一个人能活一百年，那也只相当于一千二百个月——再进一步把它拆解成日、时、分，这个数字会更令人心惊。
Why is this relevant?
这一点有什么意义呢？
Well, quite simply put: life is short.
道理很简单：人生苦短。
Spending eight hours every day in a slumber means you’re losing a third of your life to bed.
每天花八个小时睡觉，意味着你有三分之一的生命都在睡梦中度过。
So, the question is: is eight hours the exact amount we need, or is it just a myth?
那么问题来了：八小时睡眠是我们所需的准确时长，还是只是一个固有说法？
While most scientists agree that between seven and nine hours a night is the optimal amount, this is just a rough estimate.
尽管大多数科学家都认同每晚七到九小时是最佳睡眠时长，但这只是一个粗略的估算。
In truth, it’s a little more complicated than that.
事实上，实际情况要比这复杂一些。
It seems that the amount of sleep you need depends upon your age – with infants needing much more than adults.
一个人需要的睡眠时长似乎取决于年龄——婴儿需要的睡眠时间远多于成年人。
What does seem apparent is that around seven and a half hours’ sleep is a good amount.
有一点似乎很明确：每晚大约七个半小时的睡眠是比较合适的。
In a study conducted at the University of Surrey Sleep Research Centre, the effects of sleep were monitored.
萨里大学睡眠研究中心开展了一项研究，监测了睡眠带来的影响。
One group slept for six and a half and the other for seven and a half hours per night.
研究人员将受试者分为两组，一组每晚睡六个半小时，另一组睡七个半小时。
While some findings were predictable – irritation and lower concentration in the group who slept less, there were some more surprising findings. The genes of people who had less sleep were affected.
一些研究结果在意料之中——睡眠不足的一组出现了易怒、注意力下降的情况，但还有一些结果更令人惊讶：睡眠不足者的基因受到了影响。
Genes associated with inflammation, the immune system and stress response became more active.
与炎症反应、免疫系统和应激反应相关的基因变得更加活跃。
The team also observed increases in the activity of genes related to diabetes and risk of cancer.
研究团队还发现，与糖尿病和癌症风险相关的基因活性也有所上升。
One of the biggest issues is that myths regarding sleep are constantly perpetuated.
关于睡眠的错误观念一直在被不断传播，这是最棘手的问题之一。
For example, have you ever heard that you can train yourself to need less or no sleep?
比如，你有没有听过这种说法：你可以训练自己适应更少的睡眠，甚至不睡觉？
It’s simply not true.
这纯属无稽之谈。
We will always need a certain amount of sleep – eight hours might not be the exact sweet spot, and there are factors like age to take into consideration, but one thing is true – there is a certain amount we do actually need.
人类始终需要一定时长的睡眠——八小时或许并非精准的理想时长，而且还有年龄等因素需要考虑，但有一点是毋庸置疑的：我们确实需要充足的睡眠。